two hundred paçoquinhas,
I didn't sell any.
I will need to
to raise money today.
oh yes,
hi sorry
can i get it?
Can, can take.
thank you, saw?
is yours.
are you sure you can take it?
it wasn't ours,
but sure
to be one of you had to be
in truth.
I'll pick you up there as a gift.
can take?
it's a lie friend,
has disappeared
really
Water puts in the other hand,
is already in the other,
actually
it's the little pick that's the color bank code.
take the paçoquinha plus the entertainment show
and if you want to take it,
it's just us doing it as soon as they come back again.
but you need to pay first,
not like this
thousand transited to another place,
she disappeared and the
makes it appear on the other side.
or what happens
on the other hand it's not the paçoquinha
which is the pixel code.
vacillation,
because i'm undertaking uncle
do you know what happens if you pay?
look what happens,
take the paçoquinha again
for only five reais you take two paçoquinhas
another show totally free.
Can you get it?
I'm playing in two for you
it was bad?
it's peaceful us guy,
that free marketing i'm doing for you.
You don't need no man,
That man is not your man.
I just did ten count those guys over there.
oh of too much time.
we're together there.
huh?
brother caraca,
take a look at this here,
uncle has passed.
of a thousand old,
i have thirty days to set up a business
and if you want to find out how far this is going,
accompany me there.
until tomorrow,
tamo together!